<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://rachelstreater.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://rachelstreater.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2023-05-12T10:06:45+00:00</updated><id>https://rachelstreater.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Senior Machine Learning Engineer based in London
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">create a local docker instance for testing</title><link href="https://rachelstreater.github.io/blog/2023/creating-my-site/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="create a local docker instance for testing" /><published>2023-05-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://rachelstreater.github.io/blog/2023/creating-my-site</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rachelstreater.github.io/blog/2023/creating-my-site/"><![CDATA[<p>Hoodie Thundercats retro, tote bag 8-bit Godard craft beer gastropub. Truffaut Tumblr taxidermy, raw denim Kickstarter sartorial dreamcatcher. Quinoa chambray slow-carb salvia readymade, bicycle rights 90’s yr typewriter selfies letterpress cardigan vegan.</p>

<hr />

<p>Pug heirloom High Life vinyl swag, single-origin coffee four dollar toast taxidermy reprehenderit fap distillery master cleanse locavore. Est anim sapiente leggings Brooklyn ea. Thundercats locavore excepteur veniam eiusmod. Raw denim Truffaut Schlitz, migas sapiente Portland VHS twee Bushwick Marfa typewriter retro id keytar.</p>

<blockquote>
    We do not grow absolutely, chronologically. We grow sometimes in one dimension, and not in another, unevenly. We grow partially. We are relative. We are mature in one realm, childish in another.
    —Anais Nin
</blockquote>

<p>Fap aliqua qui, scenester pug Echo Park polaroid irony shabby chic ex cardigan church-key Odd Future accusamus. Blog stumptown sartorial squid, gastropub duis aesthetic Truffaut vero. Pinterest tilde twee, odio mumblecore jean shorts lumbersexual.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts" /><category term="images" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[march & april, looking forward to summer]]></summary></entry></feed>